export default questions = [
	{
		People: {
			100: {
				question: "Who is creator of Facebook and Meta?",
				answer: "Mark Zuckerberg",
			},
			200: {
				question: "Who, alongside Steve Jobs, founded Apple in 1977?",
				answer: "Steve Wozniak",
			},
			300: {
				question: "Which British Mathematician developed broke the German WWII Enigma code?",
				answer: "Alan Turing",
			},
			400: {
				question: "What european programmer is the Father of Python?",
				answer: "Guido van Rossum",
			},
			500: {
				question: "What programmer at Sun Microsystems developed Java?",
				answer: "James Gosling",
			},
		},
	},
	{
		Languages: {
			100: {
				question: "What language consists only of 1s and 0s?",
				answer: "Binary (or Machine Language)",
			},
			200: {
				question: "What language was based on a previous language called B?",
				answer: "C",
			},
			300: {
				question: "What language is Microsoft's take on C++?",
				answer: "C#",
			},
			400: {
				question: "What language is named after a British Comedy group?",
				answer: "Python",
			},
			500: {
				question: "Which language, first released in 1996, released it's LTS version 21 in 2023?",
				answer: "Java",
			},
		},
	},
	{
		Acronyms: {
			100: {
				question: "Multiple of which \"Universal\" rectangular port are present on almost all modern computers",
				answer: "USB (Universal Serial Bus)",
			},
			200: {
				question: "Which component is considered the \"Brain\" of the computer?",
				answer: "CPU (Central Processing Unit)",
			},
			300: {
				question: "Which acronym at the beginning of a website's URL indicates that it is encrypted and secure?",
				answer: "HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure)",
			},
			400: {
				question: "Which file format of short sets of image frames commonly spurs debates about its pronuncuation?",
				answer: "GIF (Graphics Interchange Format)",
			},
			500: {
				question: "Which booting architechture replaced the BIOS?",
				answer: "UEFI (Unified Extensible Firmware Interface)",
			},
		},
	},
	{
		Places: {
			100: {
				question: "Which Pacific Northwest city is home to the headquarters of Amazon?",
				answer: "Seattle",
			},
			200: {
				question: "Which Californian valley contains the headquarters of many major tech companies in cities such as Palo Alto?",
				answer: "Silicon Valley",
			},
			300: {
				question: "Other than a programming language or type of coffee, Java is also the name of an island in which country?",
				answer: "Indonesia",
			},
			400: {
				question: "Which country was Python invented in?",
				answer: "The Netherlands",
			},
			500: {
				question: "Frontier, the world's fastest supercomputer, resides in the city of Oak Ridge in which U.S. State?",
				answer: "Tennessee",
			},
		},
	},
	{
		Companies: {
			100: {
				question: "What company develops the Windows Operating Systems?",
				answer: "Microsoft",
			},
			200: {
				question: "Which electronic car company is named after a Serbian inventor?",
				answer: "Tesla",
			},
			300: {
				question: "Which Korean electronics company famous for their Galaxy phones literally means \"Three Stars\"?",
				answer: "Samsung",
			},
			400: {
				question: "Which electronics company run by Tim Cook is the world's largest company by market capitalization?",
				answer: "Apple",
			},
			500: {
				question: "Which Japanese video game company was first founded as a playing card company in 1889?",
				answer: "Nintendo",
			},
		},
	},
];
